Total Experience: 5 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Electronics/Telecommunication]

Notice Period: Currently Serving Notice Period

Yelugubanti Hemasai (1) Featured



Identity and Access Management developer, Dell One Identity Specialist, Software Development,

Application Programming, Requirement Gathering, System Analysis, Implementation, Technical Architecture.

Access Management, Agile Methodology, HTML, CSS, SQL



Current Designation: Project Engineer

Current Company: Wipro

Current Location: Hyderabad / Secunderabad

Pref. Location: Hyderabad

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: IAM developer, One Identity, Provisioning, Recertification, PAM Automation, RBAC, SoD, Access Request,

Workflows, Reporting, Auditing, User access review, SQL, VB, HTML, RTC, JIRA, Agile

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 18-Jan-21 Last Modified: 18-Jan-21

Summary

IAM developer having 5years of experience on end to end implementation, acted as Developer, Implementer, Business Analyst, Support Engineer, Scrum master, requirement gathering, on all areas on IAM domain. Involved in end to end IAM implementation of 4 projects where it covers Provisioning, Recertification, PAM Automation, RBAC, SoD, Access Request, Workflows, Reporting, Auditing, User access review.

Having 4 years of end to end experience in One Identity Manager tool and worked on Designer, Web Designer, Manager, Object browser, Job Queue, Report Editor, Transporter, Sync Editor, Data Importer, Config..etc Certified as One Identity Manager - technical specialist

Work Experience

Wipro as Project Engineer Mar 2019 to Till Date

Identity and Access Management developer, Dell One Identity Specialist, Software Development, Application Programming, Requirement Gathering, System Analysis, Implementation, Technical Architecture, Access Management, Agile Methodology, HTML, CSS, SQL

HSBC GLT as Software Engineer Nov 2015 to Mar 2019

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Electronics/Telecommunication) from SRM university (SRMU) in 2015

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs:

Dell One Identity Manager - Technical Specialist

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
SQL, HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT	
Agile, DevOps	
Dell one Identity Manager ,MS Excel	
SqlSever management studio	
Rational Team Concert	
SQL 2008R2, SQL 2012	
Quality Center, Jira	
Confluence, SharePoint	

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Telugu				

Projects

Project Title: SoD Client: Wipro

Nature of Employment: Full Time Duration: Sep 2020 - Sep 2020 Role: Sr. Programmer Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Team Size: 2

Skill Used: VB SCRIPT, SQL,

Role Description: Need to develop new requirements and monitor whole system

Project Details: SoD is an segregation of Duties to perform violations between users and SAP roles

Project Title: LORA Client: Wipro

Nature of Employment: Full Time Duration: May 2020 - Sep 2020

Role: Sr. Programmer Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Team Size: 4

Skill Used: VB SCRIPT, SQL,

Role Description: Used to developer UI, workflows, configurations

Project Details: Lean on role access, to raise SAP roles from UI portal and that needs to provisioned backend with necessary

workflows and assigned to users

Project Title: PAM Automation

Client: Wipro

Nature of Employment: Full Time Duration: Jul 2019 - May 2020 Role: Project Leader Onsite / Offsite: Offsite Team Size: 2

Skill Used: VB SCRIPT, SQL, web SQL,

Role Description: Acted as Designer, Developer, tester, implementer

Project Details: PAM automation is an project where we have handled 10 privilege accounts to be accessed and provisioned

automatically to the users.

Affirmative Action

Category: General

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time